You rolling loud like you own the place.
Dropping punch lines no one wants to
chase.
Always got a story but it's full of
holes.
Every word a show for their clueless
souls.
Say it once again. Got to flex your
grin. But you never win. You never win.
Shut it all the time just to fill the
air.
Never knowing where to zip it up.
talking like they're jeans in some
plastic chair.
Making noise but never enough.
Hey yeah. Wo wo wo.
Opinions flying faster than their cheap
guitars.
Cutting through the room just like old
cigars.
Pushing every bite until you break or
bruise.
Living for attention they will always
lose.
Spin it round and round.
Frank it up so loud but it all falls
down.
It all falls down.
Shout it all the time just to fill the
air.
Never knowing where to zip it up.
Talking like their dreams in some
plastic chair.
Making noise but never enough.
Hey. Hey. Yeah.